

# TECHINICAL SKILLS

React.JS Redux CSS Javascript HTML NodeJS SQL MongoDB

# PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Self-Motivated
Fast learner
Collaborative
Communication
Organized
Time management

#### CONTACT

E: mark.mulligan.jr1@gmail.com P: 817-504-5426 W: mark-mulligan.github.io G: github.com/Mark-Mulligan

# MARK MULLIGAN

## FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

mark.mulligan.jr1@gmail.com

817-504-5426



mark-mulligan.github.io



www.linkedin.com/in/mark-mulligan-90b4671b7

#### **ABOUT**

I am a former band director turned front end developer. I am familiar with all things react and enjoy creating amazing websites. I also have experience working on backend technologies, databases, REST APIS, and creating full stack applications.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

Freelance | 2020 - Present

• Worked with multiple clients to fulfill their vision of building a website for their personal needs or business

#### SMU CODING BOOTCAMP

Student | Sept 2020 - March 2021

• Graduated at the top of the cohort and achieved a 4.0 gpa

#### ASSITIANT BAND DIRECTOR

Frisco ISD | Sept 2018 - Present

- Experience Working in a collaborative team environment
- Planned, coordinated, and management multiple projects

#### **EDUCATION**

### BACHELOR OF ARTS, MUSIC EDUCATION

University of North Texas | 2012 - 2017 Summa Con Laude

#### SMU CODING BOOTCAMP

Southern Methodist University | 2020